

GRADE 12 STUDENT

# REGINE SISON

0999-900-3970 reginemaesison02@gmail.com

https://www.reginesison.com/ www.facebook.com/redjeanss

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

Striving to learn through actual experience and exposure. With my knowledge about user experience and the fundamentals of graphic design, I seek to discover my full potential outside my comfort zone as I collaborate with professionals, contribute to the team, and gather critical feedback for my growth.

## **SKILLS**

#### **Computer Skills**

Proficient in Canva, Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator Sketch & Draw, Blender, and Sony Vegas.

# **Working Abilities**

Organization, Communication, Leadership, Brainstorming, Analytical Thinking, Logistics, & Time Management

#### Languages

Native speaker in Filipino, Fluent in English, Proficient in Mandarin, and Beginner in Japanese

## CERTIFICATES AND HONORS

# **Technology Recognition (2019-2020)**

- UXPH National Roadshow Manila Certificate of Attendance
- Figma 101 Workshop Certificate of Completion with Anjo Cerdeña
- Google Code-In Certificate of Completion

# Academic Achievements (2015-2020)

- Aguileon Award: General average more than 93
- Jose Rizal Award: Top 3 students
- Distinction in Filipino, Theater Arts, & Math

# Co-curricular Involvement (2018)

• Scene Work: Molave and Orchid Theatre Certificate of Completion as scholar

## **WORK EXPERIENCE & PROJECTS**

#### 2020

• UX/UI designer for Google Solution Challenge Project

#### 2019

- Open source contributor in Google Code-In
  - Logo Design Sketches for CC Extractor Development
  - Teddy Bear Toy Designs for Liquid Galaxy
  - Put-On-A-Shirt Designs for Liquid Galaxy

#### 2018-2020

- Graphic designer for the multimedia needs of Mosaic BGC, Bread of Life Ministries.
- Designer and illustrator for the social media content of G\_, an organization that gathers and holds events for the youth.

## 2018-2019

Logistics "Team Muscle" volunteer for the CROSSFIT events
—Kalis Games International and Manila Throwdown.

# **EDUCATIONAL ACTIVITIES**

# The Meridian International Learning Experience (2015-2020)

- Highschool & Senior Highschool (STEM track)
- · Graduating on May 2021

# COURSERA / University of Michigan (2020)

User Experience Research & Design Online Specialization Course (Total: 6 courses)

- Introduction to User Experience Principles and Processes
- Understanding User Needs
- Evaluating Designs with Users
- UX Design: From Concept to Prototype
- · UX Research at Scale: Surveys, Analytics, Online Testing
- UX Capstone

## COURSERA / California Institute of the Arts (2020)

UI/UX Design Online Specialization Course (Total: 4 Courses)

- Visual Elements of User Interface Design
- UX Design Fundamentals
- · Web Design: Strategy and Information Architecture
- · Web Design: Wireframes to Prototypes